So what is webpack?
Ento, o que  webpack?
Webpack is a bundler but it actually is more than that, a bundler alone would just concatenate files, webpack
O Webpack  um bundler, mas na verdade  mais do que isso, um bundler sozinho apenas concatenava arquivos, o webpack
does that
faz isso,
but it also allows you to optimize your files and you hook in various plugins and so-called loaders
mas tambm permite otimizar seus arquivos e conectar vrios plugins e os chamados loaders para tambm transformar
to also transform your files
seus arquivos e para exemplo
and for example transpile next generation javascript to current generation javascript. But in its core,
transpile prxima gerao javascript para a gerao atual javascript. Mas em seu ncleo, a
the idea behind webapck is to have multiple javascript, css, image, whatever files and bundle them together.
idia por trs do webapck  ter vrios javascript, css, imagem, quaisquer arquivos e agrup-los.
It analyzes connections between these files like imports and then bundles everything together, allows
Ele analisa as conexes entre esses arquivos como importaes e, em seguida, agrupa tudo, permite otimiz-lo
you to optimize it
e, como eu
and as I said, allows you to also run some additional logic to transform your code or do whatever you
disse, permite que voc tambm execute alguma lgica adicional para transformar seu cdigo ou fazer o que
need to do with it.
for necessrio com ele.
This is what webpack does and webpack is the de-facto standard for setting up projects these days.
Isso  o que o webpack faz e o webpack  o padro de fato para a criao de projetos nos dias de hoje.
That's why we'll also use it in this module for setting up our own react workflow and project.
por isso que tambm vamos us-lo neste mdulo para configurar nosso prprio fluxo de trabalho e projeto.